



CA, USA

X anhnguyen19903@gmail.com



(714) 483 4589



http://dawnuxi.com

An Experienced Leader focused on creating design strategy and launching innovative products and services. Expert in design to empower people, solve human problems, and create delightful human-centric experience. Passionate in AR/VR, Artificial Intelligence, and Data Visualization technology.

Skills	Tools
CIVIIC	
JK III S	1001

User Experience Design Product Design Industrial Design Service Design Interaction Design Design Thinking User Research

VR/AR Design & Development Agile Development Data Visualization Information Architecture Visual Design **Concept Generation** 3D Modeling **Animation**

Rapid Prototype Website Development **Product Innovation Brand Development Usability Testing** Entrepreneurship Mobile App Development Project Management

Unity3D Cinema4D A-frame Invision Photoshop Zeplin After Effects Abstract Illustrators Mapbox Studio HTML/CSS/Javascript Sketch Solidworks Paper & Markers Figma

Trello/Jira

Experience

Design Strategy

8/2019-7/2021 Senior UX and Product Designer-Robots and Pencils Remote

Led and oversaw UX design for Financial Tech, Health Tech and EdTech projects Led a design team of 4 designers to build an end-to-end Cannabis Dispensary POS System for MJFreeway Created Northstar Vision with XR and AI Experiences for Walmart Apparel Planning and Strategy team Led design and delivered Walmart Pharmacy's Covid-19 solutions for end-to-end Associates and Customer experience Led research and design to deliver multiple end-to-end innovative solutions for associate workstream at Walmart Pharmacy to drive the mission to transform the current Clinical Services Industry

Co-Founder, CEO & Chief Designer - Virtision.com 5/2018-Present

Leading a team of 3 talented engineers from Microsoft and UIUC to build a new XR social platform for creatives Leading business, vision and innovation development as well as establishing external partnership for growth

10/2020-Present UX Design Mentor - Design Lab Remote Mentoring young UX designers around the world

Giving back to the UX Community

Pro, UX & Data Viz Designer - Corelogic Innovation Lab Santa Monica, CA

Led future innovative strategies for Big Data Visualization and Geospatial Visualization projects Led and built 2 different VR/AR prototypes to visualize Geospatial Data, Disaster Data in Real Estate Landscape. The project was featured at Corelogic's demo at EPIQ 2019.

Led UX design on 2 CEO-driven vision projects by partnering with Principal Data Strategists and leaders

8/2017-5/2018 UI/UX & VR Design Engineer - Syngenta US Innovation Lab Champaign, IL

Designed and built the lab culture to become an interactive environment for innovation

Conducted user experience research and designed web, mobile application, immersive experience

5/2017-5/2018 UI/UX & VR Intern - National Center for Supercomputing Applications Champaign, IL

Led and redesigned Advanced Visualization Lab's web interface to increase attraction and user engagement to computational

Designed user interface and produced high-quality prototypes for data visualization software collaboration with NASA.

Researched and designed Virtual Reality Controller and interfaces for AVL's Virtual Director software in order to improve Scientific Data Visualization Design's experience and workflows

Produced a demo of AVL's works to show in SIGGRAPH 2017 and got featured on Discovery Channel

Developed Virtual Reality experience on WebVR platform to showcase dome view production

Design Consultant & Front-end Developer - Cube Consulting Champaign, IL 1/2017-5/2018

Designed and developed CUBE website

2011-2013 Front-End Web Developer - Maarka Data Solutions Irvine, CA

Designed and developed better UX/UI on the company's old website

Education **Awards**

University of Illinois, at Urbana-Champaign Industrial Design - Graduated with Honors

Designation Conference Siebel Center for Design | VR Designer **UIUC's Student Employee of the Year**